Explore S&P Global

Search

EN

#### Trending Topics

#### Offerings by Division

Trending Topics

* * *

Trending Topics

Look Forward: Multidimensional Transition

Look Forward: Supply Chain 2024

AI in Banking: AI Will Be An Incremental Game Changer

The Return of Energy Security

The AI Governance Challenge

India's Future: The Quest for High and Stable Growth

* * *

Offerings by Division

* S&P Global Offerings
    
    * * *
    
* Featured Topics
    
    * * *
    
* Featured Products
    
    * * *
    
* Events
    
    * * *
    
* Careers
    
    * * *

### S&P Global Offerings

* * *

   [

#### Market Intelligence](https://ihsmarkit.com/market-intelligence/en)   [

#### Ratings](https://www.spglobal.com/ratings)   [

#### Commodity Insights](https://www.spglobal.com/commodityinsights)   [

#### S&P Dow Jones Indices](https://www.spglobal.com/spdji)   [

#### Mobility](https://www.spglobal.com/mobility)   [

#### Sustainable1](https://www.spglobal.com/esg)

### Featured Topics

* * *

### Featured Products

* * *

   [

#### S&P Capital IQ Pro](https://www.spglobal.com/marketintelligence/en/solutions/sp-capital-iq-pro)   [

#### Platts Connect](https://www.spglobal.com/commodityinsights/en/support/delivery-platforms/platts-connect)   [

#### S&P Global ESG Scores](https://www.spglobal.com/esg/solutions/data-intelligence-esg-scores)   [

#### AutoCreditInsight](https://www.spglobal.com/mobility/en/products/autocreditinsight.html)   [

#### Ratings360](https://www.spglobal.com/ratings/en/products-benefits/products/ratings360)   [

#### SPICE: The Index Source for ESG Data](https://www.spice-indices.com/)

### Events

* * *

### Careers

* * *

* S&P Global Offerings
* Featured Topics
* Featured Products
* Events
* Careers

S&P Global Offerings

   [

#### Market Intelligence](https://ihsmarkit.com/market-intelligence/en)   [

#### Ratings](https://www.spglobal.com/ratings)   [

#### Commodity Insights](https://www.spglobal.com/commodityinsights)   [

#### S&P Dow Jones Indices](https://www.spglobal.com/spdji)   [

#### Mobility](https://www.spglobal.com/mobility)   [

#### Sustainable1](https://www.spglobal.com/esg)

Featured Topics

Featured Products

   [

#### S&P Capital IQ Pro](https://www.spglobal.com/marketintelligence/en/solutions/sp-capital-iq-pro)   [

#### Platts Connect](https://www.spglobal.com/commodityinsights/en/support/delivery-platforms/platts-connect)   [

#### S&P Global ESG Scores](https://www.spglobal.com/esg/solutions/data-intelligence-esg-scores)   [

#### AutoCreditInsight](https://www.spglobal.com/mobility/en/products/autocreditinsight.html)   [

#### Ratings360](https://www.spglobal.com/ratings/en/products-benefits/products/ratings360)   [

#### SPICE: The Index Source for ESG Data](https://www.spice-indices.com/)

Events

Careers

Search EN [Support](https://www.spglobal.com/en/enterprise/about/contact-us.html)

* Explore S&P Global

* S&P Global Offerings
    
    * * *
    
* Featured Topics
    
    * * *
    
* Featured Products
    
    * * *
    
* Events
    
    * * *
    
* Careers
    
    * * *

### S&P Global Offerings

* * *

   [

#### Market Intelligence](https://ihsmarkit.com/market-intelligence/en)   [

#### Ratings](https://www.spglobal.com/ratings)   [

#### Commodity Insights](https://www.spglobal.com/commodityinsights)   [

#### S&P Dow Jones Indices](https://www.spglobal.com/spdji)   [

#### Mobility](https://www.spglobal.com/mobility)   [

#### Sustainable1](https://www.spglobal.com/esg)

### Featured Topics

* * *

### Featured Products

* * *

   [

#### S&P Capital IQ Pro](https://www.spglobal.com/marketintelligence/en/solutions/sp-capital-iq-pro)   [

#### Platts Connect](https://www.spglobal.com/commodityinsights/en/support/delivery-platforms/platts-connect)   [

#### S&P Global ESG Scores](https://www.spglobal.com/esg/solutions/data-intelligence-esg-scores)   [

#### AutoCreditInsight](https://www.spglobal.com/mobility/en/products/autocreditinsight.html)   [

#### Ratings360](https://www.spglobal.com/ratings/en/products-benefits/products/ratings360)   [

#### SPICE: The Index Source for ESG Data](https://www.spice-indices.com/)

### Events

* * *

### Careers

* * *

* S&P Global Offerings
* Featured Topics
* Featured Products
* Events
* Careers

S&P Global Offerings

   [

#### Market Intelligence](https://ihsmarkit.com/market-intelligence/en)   [

#### Ratings](https://www.spglobal.com/ratings)   [

#### Commodity Insights](https://www.spglobal.com/commodityinsights)   [

#### S&P Dow Jones Indices](https://www.spglobal.com/spdji)   [

#### Mobility](https://www.spglobal.com/mobility)   [

#### Sustainable1](https://www.spglobal.com/esg)

Featured Topics

Featured Products

   [

#### S&P Capital IQ Pro](https://www.spglobal.com/marketintelligence/en/solutions/sp-capital-iq-pro)   [

#### Platts Connect](https://www.spglobal.com/commodityinsights/en/support/delivery-platforms/platts-connect)   [

#### S&P Global ESG Scores](https://www.spglobal.com/esg/solutions/data-intelligence-esg-scores)   [

#### AutoCreditInsight](https://www.spglobal.com/mobility/en/products/autocreditinsight.html)   [

#### Ratings360](https://www.spglobal.com/ratings/en/products-benefits/products/ratings360)   [

#### SPICE: The Index Source for ESG Data](https://www.spice-indices.com/)

Events

Careers

Language

Find Products

Research & Insights

Who We Are

* Featured Products
    
    * * *

    * * *

    * * *
    
* Ratings & Benchmarks
    
    * * *

    * * *

    * * *
    
* By Topic
    
    * * *

    * * *

### Featured Products

* * *

   [

#### S&P Capital IQ Pro](https://www.spglobal.com/marketintelligence/en/solutions/sp-capital-iq-pro)   [

#### Platts Connect](https://www.spglobal.com/commodityinsights/en/support/delivery-platforms/platts-connect)   [

#### S&P Global ESG Scores](https://www.spglobal.com/esg/solutions/data-intelligence-esg-scores)   [

#### AutoCreditInsight](https://www.spglobal.com/mobility/en/products/autocreditinsight.html)   [

#### Ratings360](https://www.spglobal.com/ratings/en/products-benefits/products/ratings360)   [

#### SPICE: The Index Source for ESG Data](https://www.spice-indices.com/)

* * *

* * *

### Ratings & Benchmarks

* * *

   [

#### Overview](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/products/ratings-benchmarks)   [

#### Find a Rating](https://www.spglobal.com/ratings/en/)

* * *

* * *

### By Topic

* * *

* * *

* Featured Products
* Ratings & Benchmarks
* By Topic

Featured Products

   [

#### S&P Capital IQ Pro](https://www.spglobal.com/marketintelligence/en/solutions/sp-capital-iq-pro)   [

#### Platts Connect](https://www.spglobal.com/commodityinsights/en/support/delivery-platforms/platts-connect)   [

#### S&P Global ESG Scores](https://www.spglobal.com/esg/solutions/data-intelligence-esg-scores)   [

#### AutoCreditInsight](https://www.spglobal.com/mobility/en/products/autocreditinsight.html)   [

#### Ratings360](https://www.spglobal.com/ratings/en/products-benefits/products/ratings360)   [

#### SPICE: The Index Source for ESG Data](https://www.spice-indices.com/)

Ratings & Benchmarks

   [

#### Overview](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/products/ratings-benchmarks)   [

#### Find a Rating](https://www.spglobal.com/ratings/en/)

By Topic

* Market Insights
    
    * * *

    * * *
    
* Events
    
    * * *

    * * *

    * * *

### Market Insights

* * *

   [

#### Sustainability](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/sustainability)   [

#### Economy](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/economy)   [

#### Capital Markets](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/capital-markets)   [

#### Global Trade](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/global-trade)   [

#### Energy & Commodities](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/energy-commodities)   [

#### Technology & Innovation](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/technology-innovation)   [

#### Geopolitical Risk](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/geopolitical-risk)   [

#### Artificial Intelligence](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/artificial-intelligence)

* * *

### Events

* * *

   [

#### Featured S&P Global Events](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/events/featured)   [

#### Webinar Replays](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/events/webinar-replays)   [

#### CERAWeek](https://ceraweek.com/)

* * *

* * *

* Market Insights
* Events

Market Insights

   [

#### Sustainability](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/sustainability)   [

#### Economy](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/economy)   [

#### Capital Markets](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/capital-markets)   [

#### Global Trade](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/global-trade)   [

#### Energy & Commodities](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/energy-commodities)   [

#### Technology & Innovation](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/technology-innovation)   [

#### Geopolitical Risk](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/geopolitical-risk)   [

#### Artificial Intelligence](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/artificial-intelligence)

Events

   [

#### Featured S&P Global Events](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/events/featured)   [

#### Webinar Replays](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/events/webinar-replays)   [

#### CERAWeek](https://ceraweek.com/)

* About S&P Global
    
    * * *
    
* Corporate Responsibility
    
    * * *
    
* Diversity, Equity, & Inclusion
    
    * * *
    
* Investor Relations
    
    * * *

### About S&P Global

* * *

### Corporate Responsibility

* * *

### Diversity, Equity, & Inclusion

* * *

### Investor Relations

* * *

* About S&P Global
* Corporate Responsibility
* Diversity, Equity, & Inclusion
* Investor Relations

About S&P Global

Corporate Responsibility

Diversity, Equity, & Inclusion

Investor Relations

Back S&P Global

* Find Products
* Research & Insights
* Who We Are

* Featured Products
    
    * * *

    * * *

    * * *
    
* Ratings & Benchmarks
    
    * * *

    * * *

    * * *
    
* By Topic
    
    * * *

    * * *

### Featured Products

* * *

   [

#### S&P Capital IQ Pro](https://www.spglobal.com/marketintelligence/en/solutions/sp-capital-iq-pro)   [

#### Platts Connect](https://www.spglobal.com/commodityinsights/en/support/delivery-platforms/platts-connect)   [

#### S&P Global ESG Scores](https://www.spglobal.com/esg/solutions/data-intelligence-esg-scores)   [

#### AutoCreditInsight](https://www.spglobal.com/mobility/en/products/autocreditinsight.html)   [

#### Ratings360](https://www.spglobal.com/ratings/en/products-benefits/products/ratings360)   [

#### SPICE: The Index Source for ESG Data](https://www.spice-indices.com/)

* * *

* * *

### Ratings & Benchmarks

* * *

   [

#### Overview](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/products/ratings-benchmarks)   [

#### Find a Rating](https://www.spglobal.com/ratings/en/)

* * *

* * *

### By Topic

* * *

* * *

* Featured Products
* Ratings & Benchmarks
* By Topic

Featured Products

   [

#### S&P Capital IQ Pro](https://www.spglobal.com/marketintelligence/en/solutions/sp-capital-iq-pro)   [

#### Platts Connect](https://www.spglobal.com/commodityinsights/en/support/delivery-platforms/platts-connect)   [

#### S&P Global ESG Scores](https://www.spglobal.com/esg/solutions/data-intelligence-esg-scores)   [

#### AutoCreditInsight](https://www.spglobal.com/mobility/en/products/autocreditinsight.html)   [

#### Ratings360](https://www.spglobal.com/ratings/en/products-benefits/products/ratings360)   [

#### SPICE: The Index Source for ESG Data](https://www.spice-indices.com/)

Ratings & Benchmarks

   [

#### Overview](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/products/ratings-benchmarks)   [

#### Find a Rating](https://www.spglobal.com/ratings/en/)

By Topic

* Market Insights
    
    * * *

    * * *
    
* Events
    
    * * *

    * * *

    * * *

### Market Insights

* * *

   [

#### Sustainability](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/sustainability)   [

#### Economy](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/economy)   [

#### Capital Markets](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/capital-markets)   [

#### Global Trade](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/global-trade)   [

#### Energy & Commodities](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/energy-commodities)   [

#### Technology & Innovation](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/technology-innovation)   [

#### Geopolitical Risk](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/geopolitical-risk)   [

#### Artificial Intelligence](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/artificial-intelligence)

* * *

### Events

* * *

   [

#### Featured S&P Global Events](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/events/featured)   [

#### Webinar Replays](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/events/webinar-replays)   [

#### CERAWeek](https://ceraweek.com/)

* * *

* * *

* Market Insights
* Events

Market Insights

   [

#### Sustainability](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/sustainability)   [

#### Economy](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/economy)   [

#### Capital Markets](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/capital-markets)   [

#### Global Trade](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/global-trade)   [

#### Energy & Commodities](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/energy-commodities)   [

#### Technology & Innovation](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/technology-innovation)   [

#### Geopolitical Risk](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/geopolitical-risk)   [

#### Artificial Intelligence](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/market-insights/artificial-intelligence)

Events

   [

#### Featured S&P Global Events](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/events/featured)   [

#### Webinar Replays](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/research-insights/events/webinar-replays)   [

#### CERAWeek](https://ceraweek.com/)

* About S&P Global
    
    * * *
    
* Corporate Responsibility
    
    * * *
    
* Diversity, Equity, & Inclusion
    
    * * *
    
* Investor Relations
    
    * * *

### About S&P Global

* * *

### Corporate Responsibility

* * *

### Diversity, Equity, & Inclusion

* * *

### Investor Relations

* * *

* About S&P Global
* Corporate Responsibility
* Diversity, Equity, & Inclusion
* Investor Relations

About S&P Global

Corporate Responsibility

Diversity, Equity, & Inclusion

Investor Relations

* * *

Privacy at S&P Global
=====================

S&P Global respects your preferences concerning the collection and use of your personal information. Your privacy and trust are important to us and the following policies and statements explain how S&P Global and its subsidiaries and affiliates handle your personal information. In addition, occasionally, a specific product/service, subsidiary, or affiliate will link to a different privacy statement that will outline the particular privacy practices of that product/service, subsidiary, or affiliate.

* The [S&P Global Privacy Policy](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/privacy/privacy-policy-english) addresses information we collect at our web sites and in sales and marketing activities.
* The [S&P Global Policy for the Processing of Data Governed by the GDPR](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/legal/data-governed-gdpr) addresses our commitment to the processing of personal data under the EU General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679.
    * If you would like an executed version of this policy, [click here for a downloadable and executable version](https://ihsmarkit.com/content/dam/spglobal/corporate/en/documents/general/Legal/Policy-for-the-Processing-of-Data-Governed-by-the-GDPR.pdf), sign and email to your account representative.
* The [S&P Global Policy for the Processing of Data Governed by US Data Privacy Laws](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/legal/data-governed-ccpa) addresses our commitment to the processing of personal data under US data privacy laws.
    * If you would like an executed version of this policy, [click here for a downloadable and executable PDF version.](https://ihsmarkit.com/content/dam/spglobal/corporate/en/documents/general/Legal/Policy-for-the-Processing-of-Data-Governed-by-the-US-Data-Privacy-Laws.pdf)
* The [S&P Global Policy for the Processing of Data Governed by the PIPL](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/legal/policy-for-the-processing-of-data-governed-by-PIPL) addresses our commitment to the processing of personal data subject to the Personal Information Protection Law of the People's Republic of China.
    * If you would like an executed version of this policy, [click here for a downloadable and executable PDF version](https://ihsmarkit.com/content/dam/spglobal/corporate/en/documents/general/Legal/PIPL-Policy.pdf).
* The [S&P Global Advertising Privacy Policy](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/privacy/privacy-policy-english#tabscontainer-6aea5840b5-item-a94c9d5bbf-tab) addresses S&P Global’s policies and consumer opt-out procedures for our display advertising product, Markit Digital Advertising.
* The [S&P Global Public KYC Privacy Notice](https://ihsmarkit.com/en/legal/public-kyc-privacy-notice) provides Beneficial Owners, Key Controllers, Directors and Related Parties information about how we process personal information obtained from publicly available sources when providing Public Know Your Customer related services to our clients.
* The S&P Global Market Intelligence Privacy Notice provides Capital Markets Participants information on the inclusion of their business contact information in our comprehensive resources for capital markets professionals including how we collect, process, use, and store that information. The notice is available for data subjects in [Japan](https://dataprivacy.spglobal.com/jp/#/jp-en-privacy-notice), [日本語](https://dataprivacy.spglobal.com/jp/#/jp-privacy-notice) and [South Korea](https://dataprivacy.spglobal.com/sk/#/apac-en-privacy-notice).

Please read these policies and statements carefully. It is important that you check this site regularly as we may update these policies and statements through this site from time to time.

* Follow Us

* Our Purpose

* Investor Relations

* Contact Us

* Our Organization

* * *

Cookie Settings

* © 2024 S&P Global
